Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/calliepegadiotes (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Team Building
Skilled Multi-tasker
Pre-production

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual)

Callie Pegadiotes

Experiential Producer

San Diego, California, United States

Summary

I am a seasoned brand marketer turned freelance experiential Producer based in San Diego. I spent the first half of my career immersed in brand management and marketing and then transitioned into the production world where I thrive most and am able to apply my experience of being on the client side to how we pitch and produce experiential events. I also freelance in the music world managing AR onsite for major music festivals. I love collaborating, managing budgets and multitasking. I do best in fast paced environments and love being onsite.

Experience

Creative Riff

Producer

April 2024 - Present (11 months)

Hulu Boba Truck Comic Con 2024

Fox Universal Basic Guys Comic Con 2024 & NFL Games 2024

Good Morning America at D23 2024

Fox The Saints presented by Martin Scorcese 2024

Freelance

Freelance Event Producer | Artist Relations | Festival & Event Operations

January 2020 - Present (5 years 2 months)

San Diego Metropolitan Area

I am a highly motivated and organized go-getter who thrives in the chaos of event production. I love to be creative and collaborate/lead teams to bring brand activations and music festivals to life. I specialize in event management (logistics + site ops) and artist relations, but always love to have my hands in anything that needs it.

Google I/O 2023

Olivia Rodrigo's Vampire Premier Party 2023

YouTube Kids Reunion 2023

Bravocon 2023
Beyond Wonderland 2023
Proper NYE 2023-24
Wild Horses Fest 2023
crssd 2023
Bleached fest 2023
crssd Fall '22
day mvs '22
Under the Big Sky '22
Under the Big Sky '21
Academy of Country Music Awards 2011-2022

Self-employed Wedding Planner + Designer January 2020 - Present (5 years 2 months) San Diego, California, United States

Self-employed Brand Marketing Manager January 2020 - Present (5 years 2 months)

Seasoned brand and marketing manager with a robust background in the food & bev industry. Thrives on being creative and ideating plans to catapult brands into household names with omni-channel activations and campaigns. I especially love experiential marketing and excel in fast-paced environments where quick problem solving is necessary to successfully lead a project. I freelance with businesses, start-ups and entrepreneurs to position their brand and messaging for their ideal client. My freelance work includes design, social media strategy and execution, branded events, campaign planning and budget management.

Freelance

Artist Relations | Talent Escort
December 2010 - Present (14 years 3 months)

Artist liaison to production on live and recorded events.

Dick Clark New Year's Rockin' Eve, The Band Perry, 2011
Academy of Country Music Awards, Brantley Gilbert, 2012-2013
Dick Clark New Year's Rockin' Eve, Ellie Goulding, 2013
Academy of Country Music Awards, Brett Eldredge, 2014
Academy of Country Music Awards, Sam Hunt, 2015

Academy of Country Music Awards, Cole Swindell, 2017 Academy of Country Music Awards, Jon Pardi, 2018 Academy of Country Music Awards, Maren Morris, 2019 Spirit Awards, Robert De Niro, 2020 Academy of Country Music Awards, Luke Grimes, 2021

Callie's Captures
Lifestyle Photographer
January 2015 - January 2024 (9 years 1 month)
San Diego Metropolitan Area

Lifestyle photographer focusing on seniors/grads, pets and family

Creative Riff
Associate Producer | Sponsorships Bravocon
September 2023 - November 2023 (3 months)

MAS

Senior Production Coordinator
April 2023 - November 2023 (8 months)
Google I/O Connect Miami May 24, 2023
YouTube Shorts Olivia Rodrigo Vampire Premiere June 29, 2023
YouTube kids reunion October 2023

Compass
Marketing Advisor
October 2019 - March 2020 (6 months)
Los Angeles Metropolitan Area

*Laid off due to COVID-19

Led marketing, digital + social strategy for 70+ agents in the Westlake Region
Developed + executed multi-channel marketing plans including influencer
programs + external partnerships
Managed timelines + deadlines for 5 large agent teams
Optimized the marketing processes for quicker turnaround
Designed marketing + social collateral for several agent teams using Adobe
suite

Created print + digital marketing materials

Treasury Wine Estates
Global Associate Brand Manager, 19 Crimes Wine
June 2018 - October 2019 (1 year 5 months)
Page 3 of 5

Oakland, CA

Relocated to Los Angeles Oct 2019

Successfully launched 8 products in less than 2 years

Maintained double-digit sales growth through innovative product launches + creative marketing plans globally

Partnered with creative agency to grow social by 600% in 12 months Managed relationship with Digital Team to ensure success of AR app, a feature the brand pioneered in its category

Utilized insights + data to strategize 360 marketing campaigns that drove brand awareness to increase 10 points in 1 year

Acted as a strategic lead to global + regional marketing teams

Led partnership with creative agencies on all creative content across all channels

Cross-functionally managed influencer programming

Albertsons Companies

Assistant Brand Marketing Manager, Own Brands Portfolio March 2016 - May 2018 (2 years 3 months)

Pleasanton, CA

Strategized + executed national marketing campaigns for an \$11B portfolio of private-label brands

Designed + implemented "New & Exclusive Campaign"

Spearheaded strategy for digital offers on loyalty platforms

Executed a variety of ad hoc projects due to a lean team

Creative director on all marketing campaign collateral + digital assets

Led brand team in the production of a national commercial spot for O Organics

from pre-production to air

Hungry Girl, Inc.

Innovation & Creative Content Producer, Photographer, Food Stylist July 2009 - January 2016 (6 years 7 months)

Los Angeles, CA

Led recipe development + content creation for 9 New York Times bestselling cookbooks

Assisted in the development, design + go-to-market strategy for product + book launches

Creative director for all external shoots

Managed test kitchen + all incoming products for review

Built the in-house photography studio

Styled + photographed all recipe + product photos

Led cross-functional teams through the production live of recorded TV segments

One of three who led all in-house nutritional calculations on all recipes produced

Fact checked all digital and print assets

Cox Media

Production Intern

January 2009 - May 2009 (5 months)

Greater San Diego Area

- Assisted in production of 10+ local commercials.
- o Distributed and edited schedules and scripts to crew.
- o Served as Assistant Camera Operator.
- o Set up lighting.
- o Assistant editor using Final Cut Pro.
- · Voice over talent.

Education

San Diego State University-California State University
Bachelor of Arts (B.A.), Communication and Media Studies · (2007 - 2009)

Las Positas College

· (2005 - 2007)